CAMERON F. RUSSO

cfrusso18@gmail.com

Game Developer – Boston, MA

781-572-8249 | Xephyre#2257

www.cameronrusso.com | linkedin.com/in/cfrusso18 | github.com/cfrusso18 | twitter.com/Xephyre18

SUMMARY

Hello! I am Cam, and I'm a 22-year-old recent graduate of Northeastern University, graduating with a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Game Development in May of 2023. For the past four years at school, I have been creating and learning about games, as well as sharing my knowledge as a board member for the Northeastern University Game Development Club.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES: C++, C#, Java, C, Python, Lua, Unreal Blueprints, TypeScript, React, Assembly, HTML **SOFTWARE:** Unity, Unreal Engine 5, Git, Adobe Suite, Visual Studio, JetBrains IDEs, Godot, Ren'Py

EXPERIENCE

Wayfair, Boston, MA

June 2021 - December 2021

IT Asset Management, Co-Op

- Responsible for distribution, reclamation, and repair of all technological equipment
- Managed projects to improve the workflow of our team
- Assisted in the organization and execution of Wayfair's Return To Office

Target, Danvers, MA

June 2020-August 2020

Seasonal Fulfillment Expert

- Completed orders made to the store for in-store pickup and prepared order for shipping
- Optimized fulfillment process due to strong emphasis on efficiency

Eastern Massachusetts Lacrosse Officials Association, Stoneham, MA Senior Associate Official

April 2016-June 2019

- Refereed youth lacrosse games at the U9, U11, U13, and U15 levels
- Responsible for teaching new Associate Officials in game scenarios
- Upheld the integrity of the game and assured the safety of everyone involved

Education

Northeastern University, Boston, MA

September 2019-Present

Khoury College of Computer Sciences

Candidate for Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Game Development GPA: 3.6/4.0

Coursework: Game Studio, Level Design, Game Engines, Game Narrative, Rapid Idea Prototyping Stoneham High School, Stoneham, MA August 2015-May 2019

Activities

Projects: SUPERULTRAMEGA FIGHT!!!!!!!! (Unity, Fighting), Antithesis (Unity VR, 1v1 Competitive Horror) Hobbies: Video Games (fighting, RPG, strategy), fitness, cooking, trumpet, modding consoles, cheese